<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (B5) on Nano Guides</title>
    <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-order-of-the-phoenix-b5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (B5) on Nano Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:38:19 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-order-of-the-phoenix-b5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C38)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:38:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-38/</guid>
      <description>The Second War Begins HE WHO MUST NOT BE NAMED RETURNS &amp;lsquo;In a brief statement on Friday night, Minister for Magic Cornelius Fudge confirmed that He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named has returned to this country and is once more active.
&amp;rsquo;&amp;ldquo;It is with great regret that I must confirm that the wizard styling himself Lord&amp;ndash;well, you know who I mean&amp;ndash;is alive and among us again,&amp;rdquo; said Fudge, looking tired and flustered as he addressed reporters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C37)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:37:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-37/</guid>
      <description>The Lost Prophecy Harry&amp;rsquo;s feet hit solid ground; his knees buckled a little and the golden wizard&amp;rsquo;s head fell with a resounding clunk to the floor. He looked around and saw that he had arrived in Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s office.
Everything seemed to have repaired itself during the Headmasters absence. The delicate silver instruments stood once more on the spindle-legged tables, puffing and whirring serenely. The portraits of the headmasters and headmistresses were snoozing in their frames, heads lolling back in armchairs or against the edge of the picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C36)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:36:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-36/</guid>
      <description>The Only One He Ever Feared &amp;lsquo;He hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone!&amp;rsquo; Harry yelled.
He did not believe it; he would not believe it; still he fought Lupin with every bit of strength he had. Lupin did not understand; people hid behind that curtain; Harry had heard them whispering the first time he had entered the room. Sirius was hiding, simply lurking out of sight&amp;ndash;
&amp;lsquo;SIRIUS!&amp;rsquo; he bellowed. &amp;lsquo;SIRIUS!&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;He can&amp;rsquo;t come back, Harry,&amp;rsquo; said Lupin, his voice breaking as he struggled to contain Harry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C35)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:35:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-35/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the Veil Black shapes were emerging out of thin air all around them, blocking their way left and right; eyes glinted through slits in hoods, a dozen lit wand tips were pointing directly at their hearts; Ginny gave a gasp of horror.
&amp;lsquo;To me, Potter,&amp;rsquo; repeated the drawling voice of Lucius Malfoy as he held out his hand, palm up.
Harry&amp;rsquo;s insides plummeted sickeningly. They were trapped, and outnumbered two to one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C34)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:34:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-34/</guid>
      <description>The Department of Mysteries Harry wound his hand tightly into the mane of the nearest Thestral, placed a foot on a stump nearby and scrambled clumsily on to the horse&amp;rsquo;s silken back. It did not object, but twisted its head around, fangs bared, and attempted to continue its eager licking of his robes.
He found there was a way of lodging his knees behind the wing joints that made him feel more secure, then looked around at the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C33)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:33:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-33/</guid>
      <description>Fight and Flight Harry had no idea what Hermione was planning, or even whether she had a plan. He walked half a pace behind her as they headed down the corridor outside Umbridge&amp;rsquo;s office, knowing it would look very suspicious if he appeared not to know where they were going. He did not dare attempt to talk to her; Umbridge was walking so closely behind them that he could hear her ragged breathing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C32)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:32:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-32/</guid>
      <description>Out of the Fire &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not going &amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t need the hospital wing &amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t want &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;
He was gibbering as he tried to pull away from Professor Tofty, who was looking at Harry with much concern after helping him out into the Entrance Hall with the students all around them staring.
I&amp;rsquo;m&amp;ndash;I&amp;rsquo;m fine, sir,&amp;rsquo; Harry stammered, wiping the sweat from his face. &amp;lsquo;Really &amp;hellip; I just fell asleep &amp;hellip; had a nightmare &amp;hellip; &amp;lsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C31)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:31:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-31/</guid>
      <description>Owls Ron&amp;rsquo;s euphoria at helping Gryffindor scrape the Quidditch cup was such that he couldn&amp;rsquo;t settle to anything next day. All he wanted to do was talk over the match, so Harry and Hermione found it very difficult to find an opening in which to mention Grawp. Not that either of them tried very hard; neither was keen to be the one to bring Ron back to reality in quite such a brutal fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C30)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:30:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-30/</guid>
      <description>Grawp The story of Fred and George&amp;rsquo;s flight to freedom was retold so often over the next few days that Harry could tell it would soon become the stuff of Hogwart&amp;rsquo;s legend: within a week, even those who had been eye-witnesses were half-convinced they had seen the twins dive-bomb Umbridge on their brooms and pelt her with Dungbombs before zooming out of the doors. In the immediate aftermath of their departure there was a great wave of talk about copying them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (C29)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 19:29:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/order-of-the-phoenix-b5/chapter-29/</guid>
      <description>Careers Advice &amp;lsquo;But why haven&amp;rsquo;t you got Occlumency lessons any more?&amp;rsquo; said Hermione, frowning.
&amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve told you,&amp;rsquo; Harry muttered. &amp;lsquo;Snape reckons I can carry on by myself now I&amp;rsquo;ve got the basics. &amp;lsquo;
&amp;lsquo;So you&amp;rsquo;ve stopped having funny dreams?&amp;rsquo; said Hermione sceptically.
&amp;lsquo;Pretty much,&amp;rsquo; said Harry, not looking at her.
&amp;lsquo;Well, I don&amp;rsquo;t think Snape should stop until you&amp;rsquo;re absolutely sure you can control them!&amp;rsquo; said Hermione indignantly. &amp;lsquo;Harry, I think you should go back to him and ask&amp;ndash; &amp;lsquo;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>