<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Goblet of Fire (B4) on Nano Guides</title>
    <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/tags/goblet-of-fire-b4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Goblet of Fire (B4) on Nano Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:37 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://HBTghost.github.io/tags/goblet-of-fire-b4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C37)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-37/</guid>
      <description>The Beginning When he looked back, even a month later, Harry found he had only scattered memories of the next few days. It was as though he had been through too much to take in any more. The recollections he did have were very painful. The worst, perhaps, was the meeting with the Diggory&amp;rsquo;s that took place the following morning.
They did not blame him for what had happened; on the contrary, both thanked him for returning Cedric&amp;rsquo;s body to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C36)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-36/</guid>
      <description>The Parting of the Ways Dumbledore stood up. He stared down at Barty Crouch for a moment with disgust on his face. Then he raised his wand once more and ropes flew out of it, ropes that twisted themselves around Barty Crouch, binding him tightly. He turned to Professor McGonagall.
&amp;ldquo;Minerva, could I ask you to stand guard here while I take Harry upstairs?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Of course,&amp;rdquo; said Professor McGonagall. She looked slightly nauseous, as though she had just watched someone being sick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C35)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-35/</guid>
      <description>Veritaserum Harry felt himself slam flat into the ground; his face was pressed into grass; the smell of it filled his nostrils. He had closed his eyes while the Portkey transported him, and he kept them closed now. He did not move. All the breath seemed to have been knocked out of him; his head was swimming so badly he felt as though the ground beneath him were swaying like the deck of a ship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C34)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-34/</guid>
      <description>Priori Incantatem Wormtail approached Harry, who scrambled to find his feet, to support his own weight before the ropes were untied. Wormtail raised his new silver hand, pulled out the wad of material gagging Harry, and then, with one swipe, cut through the bonds tying Harry to the gravestone.
There was a split second, perhaps, when Harry might have considered running for it, but his injured leg shook under him as he stood on the overgrown grave, as the Death Eaters closed ranks, forming a tighter circle around him and Voldemort, so that the gaps where the missing Death Eaters should have stood were filled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C33)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-33/</guid>
      <description>The Death Eaters Voldemort looked away from Harry and began examining his own body. His hands were like large, pale spiders; his long white fingers caressed his own chest, his arms, his face; the red eyes, whose pupils were slits, like a cats, gleamed still more brightly through the darkness. He held up his hands and flexed the fingers, his expression rapt and exultant. He took not the slightest notice of Wormtail, who lay twitching and bleeding on the ground, nor of the great snake, which had slithered back into sight and was circling Harry again, hissing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C32)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:32 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-32/</guid>
      <description>Flesh, Blood, and Bone Harry felt his feet slam into the ground; his injured leg gave way, and he fell forward; his hand let go of the Triwizard Cup at last. He raised his head.
&amp;ldquo;Where are we?&amp;rdquo; he said.
Cedric shook his head. He got up, pulled Harry to his feet, and they looked around.
They had left the Hogwarts grounds completely; they had obviously traveled miles - perhaps hundreds of miles - for even the mountains surrounding the castle were gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C31)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:31 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-31/</guid>
      <description>The Third Task &amp;ldquo;Dumbledore reckons You-Know-Who&amp;rsquo;s getting stronger again as well?&amp;rdquo; Ron whispered.
Everything Harry had seen in the Pensieve, nearly everything Dumbledore had told and shown him afterward, he had now shared with Ron and Hermione - and, of course, with Sirius, to whom Harry had sent an owl the moment he had left Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s office. Harry, Ron, and Hermione sat up late in the common room once again that night, talking it all over until Harry&amp;rsquo;s mind was reeling, until he understood what Dumbledore had meant about a head becoming so full of thoughts that it would have been a relief to siphon them off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C30)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-30/</guid>
      <description>The Pensieve The door of the office opened.
&amp;ldquo;Hello, Potter,&amp;rdquo; said Moody. &amp;ldquo;Come in, then. &amp;ldquo;
Harry walked inside. He had been inside Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s office once before; it was a very beautiful, circular room, lined with pictures of previous headmasters and headmistresses of Hogwarts, all of whom were fast asleep, their chests rising and falling gently.
Cornelius Fudge was standing beside Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s desk, wearing his usual pinstriped cloak and holding his lime-green bowler hat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C29)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-29/</guid>
      <description>The Dream It comes down to this,&amp;rdquo; said Hermione, rubbing her forehead. &amp;ldquo;Either Mr. Crouch attacked Viktor, or somebody else attacked both of them when Viktor wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;It must&amp;rsquo;ve been Crouch,&amp;rdquo; said Ron at once. &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s why he was gone when Harry and Dumbledore got there. He&amp;rsquo;d done a runner. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t think so,&amp;rdquo; said Harry, shaking his head. &amp;ldquo;He seemed really weak - I don&amp;rsquo;t reckon he was up to Disapparating or anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire (C28)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 13:38:28 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/goblet-of-fire-b4/chapter-28/</guid>
      <description>The Madness of Mr Crouch Harry, Ron, and Hermione went up to the Owlery after breakfast on Sunday to send a letter to Percy, asking, as Sirius had suggested, whether he had seen Mr. Crouch lately. They used Hedwig, because it had been so long since she&amp;rsquo;d had a job. When they had watched her fly out of sight through the Owlery window, they proceeded down to the kitchen to give Dobby his new socks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>