<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (B3) on Nano Guides</title>
    <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (B3) on Nano Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:22:09 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C22)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:22:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-22/</guid>
      <description>Owl Post Again &amp;ldquo;Harry!&amp;rdquo;
Hermione was tugging at his sleeve, staring at her watch. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve got exactly ten minutes to get back down to the hospital wing without anybody seeing us &amp;ndash; before Dumbledore locks the door &amp;ndash;&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Okay,&amp;rdquo; said Harry, wrenching his gaze from the sky, &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s go&amp;hellip; . &amp;ldquo;
They slipped through the doorway behind them and down a tightly spiraling stone staircase. As they reached the bottom of it, they heard voices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C21)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:21:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-21/</guid>
      <description>Hermiones Secret &amp;ldquo;Shocking business&amp;hellip; shocking&amp;hellip; miracle none of them died&amp;hellip; never heard the like&amp;hellip; by thunder, it was lucky you were there, Snape&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Thank you, Minister. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Order of Merlin, Second Class, I&amp;rsquo;d say. First Class, if I can wangle it!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Thank you very much indeed, Minister. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Nasty cut you&amp;rsquo;ve got there&amp;hellip; Black&amp;rsquo;s work, I suppose?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;As a matter of fact, it was Potter, Weasley, and Granger, Minister&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C20)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:20:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-20/</guid>
      <description>The Dementors Kiss Harry had never been part of a stranger group. Crookshanks led the way down the stairs; Lupin, Pettigrew, and Ron went next, looking like entrants in a six-legged race. Next came Professor Snape, drifting creepily along, his toes hitting each stair as they descended, held up by his own wand, which was being pointed at him by Sirius. Harry and Hermione brought up the rear.
Getting back into the tunnel was difficult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C19)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:19:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-19/</guid>
      <description>The Servant of Lord Voldemort Hermione screamed. Black leapt to his feet. Harry felt as though he&amp;rsquo;d received a huge electric shock.
&amp;ldquo;I found this at the base of the Whomping Willow,&amp;rdquo; said Snape, throwing the cloak aside, careful to keep this wand pointing directly at Lupin&amp;rsquo;s chest. &amp;ldquo;Very useful, Potter, I thank you&amp;hellip; . &amp;ldquo;
Snape was slightly breathless, but his face was full of suppressed triumph. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re wondering, perhaps, how I knew you were here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C18)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:18:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-18/</guid>
      <description>Moony, Wormtail, Padfoot, and Prongs It took a few seconds for the absurdity of this statement to sink in. Then Ron voiced what Harry was thinking.
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re both mental. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Ridiculous!&amp;rdquo; said Hermione faintly.
&amp;ldquo;Peter Pettigrew&amp;rsquo;s dead!&amp;rdquo; said Harry. &amp;ldquo;He killed him twelve years ago!&amp;rdquo; He pointed at Black, whose face twitched convulsively.
&amp;ldquo;I meant to,&amp;rdquo; he growled, his yellow teeth bared, &amp;ldquo;but little Peter got the better of me&amp;hellip; not this time, though!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C17)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:17:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-17/</guid>
      <description>Cat, Rat, and Dog Harry&amp;rsquo;s mind had gone blank with shock. The three of them stood transfixed with horror under the Invisibility Cloak. The very last rays of the setting sun were casting a bloody light over the long-shadowed grounds. Then, behind them, they heard a wild howling.
&amp;ldquo;Hagrid,&amp;rdquo; Harry muttered. Without thinking about what he was doing, he made to turn back, but both Ron and Hermione seized his arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C16)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:16:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-16/</guid>
      <description>Professor Trelawneys Prediction Harry&amp;rsquo;s euphoria at finally winning the Quidditch Cup lasted at least a week. Even the weather seemed to be celebrating; as June approached, the days became cloudless and sultry, and all anybody felt like doing was strolling onto the grounds and flopping down on the grass with several pints of iced pumpkin juice, perhaps playing a casual game of Gobstones or watching the giant squid propel itself dreamily across the surface of the lake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C15)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:15:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-15/</guid>
      <description>The Quidditch Final &amp;ldquo;He sent me this,&amp;rdquo; Hermione said, holding out the letter.
Harry took it. The parchment was damp, and enormous teardrops had smudged the ink so badly in places that it was very difficult to read.
Dear Hermione, We lost. I&amp;rsquo;m allowed to bring him back to Hogwarts. Execution date to be fixed. Beaky has enjoyed London. I won&amp;rsquo;t forget all the help you gave us. Hagrid &amp;ldquo;They can&amp;rsquo;t do this,&amp;rdquo; said Harry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C14)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:14:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-14/</guid>
      <description>Snapes Grudge No one in Gryffindor Tower slept that night. They knew that the castle was being searched again, and the whole House stayed awake in the common room, waiting to hear whether Black had been caught. Professor McGonagall came back at dawn, to tell them that he had again escaped.
Throughout the day, everywhere they went they saw signs of tighter security; Professor Flitwick could be seen teaching the front doors to recognize a large picture of Sirius Black; Filch was suddenly bustling up and down the corridors, boarding up everything from tiny cracks in the walls to mouse holes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (C13)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 15:13:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/prisoner-of-azkaban-b3/chapter-13/</guid>
      <description>Gryffindor Versus Ravenclaw It looked like the end of Ron and Hermione&amp;rsquo;s friendship. Each was so angry with the other that Harry couldn&amp;rsquo;t see how they&amp;rsquo;d ever make up.
Ron was enraged that Hermione had never taken Crookshanks&amp;rsquo;s attempts to eat Scabbers seriously, hadn&amp;rsquo;t bothered to keep a close enough watch on him, and was still trying to pretend that Crookshanks was innocent by suggesting that Ron look for Scabbers under all the boys&amp;rsquo; beds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>