<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harry Potter on Nano Guides</title>
    <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Harry Potter on Nano Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:36:01 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C36)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:36:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-36/</guid>
      <description>THE FLAW IN THE PLAN He was lying facedown on the ground again. The smell of the forest filled his nostrils. He could feel the cold hard ground beneath his cheek, and the hinge of his glasses, which had been knocked sideways by the fall, cutting into his temple. Every inch of him ached, and the place where the Killing Curse had hit him felt like the bruise of an iron-clad punch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C35)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:35:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-35/</guid>
      <description>KING’S CROSS He lay facedown, listening to the silence. He was perfectly alone. Nobody was watching. Nobody else was there. He was not perfectly sure that he was there himself.
A long time later, or maybe no time at all, it came to him that he must exist, must be more than disembodied thought, because he was lying, definitely lying, on some surface. Therefore he had a sense of touch, and the thing against which he lay existed too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C34)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:34:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-34/</guid>
      <description>THE FOREST AGAIN Finally, the truth. Lying with his face pressed into the dusty carpet of the office where he had once thought he was learning the secrets of victory, Harry understood at last that he was not supposed to survive. His job was to walk calmly into Death’s welcoming arms. Along the way, he was to dispose of Voldemort’s remaining links to life, so that when at last he flung himself across Voldemort’s path, and did not raise a wand to defend himself, the end would be clean, and the job that ought to have been done in Godric’s Hollow would be finished: Neither would live, neither could survive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C33)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:33:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-33/</guid>
      <description>THE PRINCE’S TALE Harry remained kneeling at Snape’s side, simply staring down at him, until quite suddenly a high, cold voice spoke so close to them that Harry jumped to his feet, the flask gripped tightly in his hands, thinking that Voldemort had reentered the room.
Voldemort’s voice reverberated from the walls and floor, and Harry realized that he was talking to Hogwarts and to all the surrounding area, that the residents of Hogsmeade and all those still fighting in the castle would hear him as clearly as if he stood beside them, his breath on the back of their necks, a deathblow away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C32)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:32:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-32/</guid>
      <description>THE ELDER WAND The world had ended, so why had the battle not ceased, the castle fallen silent in horror, and every combatant laid down their arms? Harry’s mind was in free fall, spinning out of control, unable to grasp the impossibility, because Fred Weasley could not be dead, the evidence of all his senses must be lying —
And then a body fell past the hole blown into the side of the school, and curses flew in at them from the darkness, hitting the wall behind their heads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C31)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:31:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-31/</guid>
      <description>THE BATTLE OF HOGWARTS The enchanted ceiling of the Great Hall was dark and scattered with stars, and below it the four long House tables were lined with disheveled students, some in traveling cloaks, others in dressing gowns. Here and there shone the pearly white figures of the school ghosts. Every eye, living and dead, was fixed upon Professor McGonagall, who was speaking from the raised platform at the top of the Hall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C30)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:30:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-30/</guid>
      <description>THE SACKING OF SEVERUS SNAPE The moment her finger touched the Mark, Harry’s scar burned savagely, the starry room vanished from sight, and he was standing upon an outcrop of rock beneath a cliff, and the sea was washing around him and there was triumph in his heart — They have the boy.
A loud bang brought Harry back to where he stood: Disoriented, he raised his wand, but the witch before him was already falling forward; she hit the ground so hard that the glass in the bookcases tinkled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C29)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:29:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-29/</guid>
      <description>THE LOST DIADEM Neville — what the — how — ?”
But Neville had spotted Ron and Hermione, and with yells of delight was hugging them too. The longer Harry looked at Neville, the worse he appeared: One of his eyes was swollen yellow and purple, there were gouge marks on his face, and his general air of unkemptness suggested that he had been living rough. Nevertheless, his battered visage shone with happiness as he let go of Hermione and said again, “I knew you’d come!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C28)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:28:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-28/</guid>
      <description>THE MISSING MIRROR Harry’s feet touched road. He saw the achingly familiar Hogsmeade High Street: dark shop fronts, and the outline of black mountains beyond the village, and the curve in the road ahead that led off toward Hogwarts, and light spilling from the windows of the Three Broomsticks, and with a lurch of the heart he remembered, with piercing accuracy, how he had landed here nearly a year before, supporting a desperately weak Dumbledore; all this in a second, upon landing — and then, even as he relaxed his grip upon Ron’s and Hermione’s arms, it happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows (C27)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:27:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/deathly-hallows-b7/chapter-27/</guid>
      <description>THE FINAL HIDING PLACE There was no means of steering; the dragon could not see where it was going, and Harry knew that if it turned sharply or rolled in midair they would find it impossible to cling onto its broad back. Nevertheless, as they climbed higher and higher, London unfurling below them like a gray-and-green map, Harry’s overwhelming feeling was of gratitude for an escape that had seemed impossible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>