<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (B6) on Nano Guides</title>
    <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-half-blood-prince-b6/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (B6) on Nano Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:30:01 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-half-blood-prince-b6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C30)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:30:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-30/</guid>
      <description>The White Tomb All lessons were suspended, all examinations postponed. Some students were hurried away from Hogwarts by their parents over the next couple of days&amp;ndash;the Patil twins were gone before breakfast on the morning following Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s death and Zacharias Smith was escorted from the castle by his haughty-looking father. Seamus Finnigan, on the other hand, refused point-blank to accompany his mother home; they had a shouting match in the Entrance Hall which was resolved when she agreed that he could remain behind for the funeral.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C29)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:29:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-29/</guid>
      <description>The Pheonix Lament &amp;ldquo;C&amp;rsquo;mere, Harry &amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;No. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yeh can&amp;rsquo; stay here, Harry&amp;hellip; come on, now&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;No. &amp;ldquo;
He did not want to leave Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s side, he did not want to move anywhere. Hagrid&amp;rsquo;s hand on his shoulder was trembling. Then another voice said, &amp;ldquo;Harry, come on. &amp;ldquo;
A much smaller and warmer hand had enclosed his and was pulling him upward. He obeyed its pressure without really thinking about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C28)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:28:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-28/</guid>
      <description>Flight of the Prince Harry felt as though he too were hurtling through space; it had not happened&amp;hellip; it could not have happened&amp;hellip;
&amp;ldquo;Out of here, quickly,&amp;rdquo; said Snape.
He seized Malfoy by the scruff of the neck and forced him through the door ahead of the rest; Greyback and the squat brother and sister followed, the latter both panting excitedly. As they vanished through the door, Harry realized he could move again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C27)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:27:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-27/</guid>
      <description>The Lightning-struck Tower Once back under the starry sky, Harry heaved Dumbledore on to the top of the nearest boulder and then to his feet. Sodden and shivering, Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s weight still upon him, Harry concentrated harder than he had ever done upon his destination: Hogsmeade. Closing his eyes, gripping Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s arm as tightly as he could, he stepped forwards into that feeling of horrible compression.
He knew it had worked before he opened his eyes: the smell of salt, the sea breeze had gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C26)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:26:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-26/</guid>
      <description>The Cave Harry could smell salt and hear rushing waves; a light, chilly breeze ruffled his hair as he looked out at moonlit sea and star-strewn sky. He was standing upon a high outcrop of dark rock, water foaming and churning below him. He glanced over his shoulder. A towering cliff stood behind them, a sheer drop, black and faceless. A few large chunks of rock, such as the one upon which Harry and Dumbledore were standing, looked as though they had broken away from the cliff face at some point in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C25)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:25:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-25/</guid>
      <description>The Seer Overheard The fact that Harry Potter was going out with Ginny Weasley seemed to interest a great number of people, most of them girls, yet Harry found himself newly and happily impervious to gossip over the next few weeks. After all, it made a very nice change to be talked about because of something that was making him happier than he could remember being for a very long time, rather than because he had been involved in horrific scenes of Dark magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C24)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:24:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-24/</guid>
      <description>Sectumsempra Exhausted but delighted with his night&amp;rsquo;s work, Harry told Ron and Hermione everything that had happened during next morning&amp;rsquo;s Charms lesson (having first cast the Muffliato spell upon those nearest them). They were both satisfyingly impressed by the way he had wheedled the memory out of Slughorn and positively awed when he told them about Voldemort&amp;rsquo;s Horcruxes and Dumbledore&amp;rsquo;s promise to take Harry along, should he find another one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C23)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:23:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-23/</guid>
      <description>Horcruxes Harry could feel the Felix Felicis wearing off as he creeped back into the castle. The front door had remainedun locked for him, but on the third floor he met Peeves and only narrowly avoided detection by diving sideways through one of his shortcuts. By the time he got up to the portrait of the Fat Lady and pulled off his Invisibility Cloak, he was not surprised to find her in a most unhelpful mood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C22)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:22:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-22/</guid>
      <description>After the Burial Patches of bright blue sky were beginning to appear over the castle turrets, but these signs of approaching summer did not lift Harry&amp;rsquo;s mood. He had been thwarted, both in his attempts to find out what Malfoy was doing, and in his efforts to start a conversation with Slughorn that might lead, somehow, to Slughorn handing over the memory he had apparently suppressed for decades.
&amp;ldquo;For the last time, just forget about Malfoy,&amp;rdquo; Hermione told Harry firmly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince (C21)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:21:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/half-blood-prince-b6/chapter-21/</guid>
      <description>The Unknowable Room Harry wracked his brains over the next week as to how he was to persuade Slughorn to hand over the true memory, but nothing in the nature of a brain wave occurred and he was reduced to doing what he did increasingly these days when at a loss: poring over his Potions book, hoping that the Prince would have scribbled something useful in a margin, as he had done so many times before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>