<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (B1) on Nano Guides</title>
    <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-philosophers-stone-b1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (B1) on Nano Guides</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:18:16 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://HBTghost.github.io/series/harry-potter-and-the-philosophers-stone-b1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C17)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:18:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-17/</guid>
      <description>The Man with Two Faces It was Quirrell.
&amp;ldquo;You!&amp;rdquo; gasped Harry.
Quirrell smiled. His face wasn&amp;rsquo;t twitching at all.
&amp;ldquo;Me,&amp;rdquo; he said calmly. &amp;ldquo;I wondered whether I&amp;rsquo;d be meeting you here, Potter. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;But I thought &amp;ndash; Snape&amp;ndash;&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Severus?&amp;rdquo; Quirrell laughed, and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t his usual quivering treble, either, but cold and sharp. &amp;ldquo;Yes, Severus does seem the type, doesn&amp;rsquo;t he? So useful to have him swooping around like an overgrown bat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C16)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:17:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-16/</guid>
      <description>Through the Trapdoor In years to come, Harry would never quite remember how he had managed to get through his exams when he half expected Voldemort to come bursting through the door at any moment. Yet the days crept by, and there could be no doubt that Fluffy was still alive and well behind the locked door.
It was sweltering hot, especially in the large classroom where they did their written papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C15)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:16:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-15/</guid>
      <description>The Forbidden Forest Things couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been worse.
Filch took them down to Professor McGonagall&amp;rsquo;s study on the first floor, where they sat and waited without saying a word to each other. Hermione was trembling. Excuses, alibis, and wild cover-up stories chased each other around Harry&amp;rsquo;s brain, each more feeble than the last. He couldn&amp;rsquo;t see how they were going to get out of trouble this time. They were cornered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C14)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:15:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-14/</guid>
      <description>Norbert the Norwegian Ridgeback Quirrell, however, must have been braver than they&amp;rsquo;d thought. In the weeks that followed he did seem to be getting paler and thinner, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t look as though he&amp;rsquo;d cracked yet.
Every time they passed the third-floor corridor, Harry, Ron, and Hermione would press their ears to the door to check that Fluffy was still growling inside. Snape was sweeping about in his usual bad temper, which surely meant that the Stone was still safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C13)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:14:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-13/</guid>
      <description>Nicholas Flamel Dumbledore had convinced Harry not to go looking for the Mirror of Erised again, and for the rest of the Christmas holidays the invisibility cloak stayed folded at the bottom of his trunk. Harry wished he could forget what he&amp;rsquo;d seen in the mirror as easily, but he couldn&amp;rsquo;t. He started having nightmares. Over and over again he dreamed about his parents disappearing in a flash of green light, while a high voice cackled with laughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C12)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:13:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-12/</guid>
      <description>The Mirror of Erised Christmas was coming. One morning in mid-December, Hogwarts woke to find itself covered in several feet of snow. The lake froze solid and the Weasley twins were punished for bewitching several snowballs so that they followed Quirrell around, bouncing off the back of his turban. The few owls that managed to battle their way through the stormy sky to deliver mail had to be nursed back to health by Hagrid before they could fly off again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C11)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:12:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-11/</guid>
      <description>Quidditch As they entered November, the weather turned very cold. The mountains around the school became icy gray and the lake like chilled steel. Every morning the ground was covered in frost. Hagrid could be seen from the upstairs windows defrosting broomsticks on the Quidditch field, bundled up in a long moleskin overcoat, rabbit fur gloves, and enormous beaverskin boots.
The Quidditch season had begun. On Saturday, Harry would be playing in his first match after weeks of training: Gryffindor versus Slytherin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C10)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:11:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-10/</guid>
      <description>Halloween Malfoy couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe his eyes when he saw that Harry and Ron were still at Hogwarts the next day, looking tired but perfectly cheerful. Indeed, by the next morning Harry and Ron thought that meeting the three-headed dog had been an excellent adventure, and they were quite keen to have another one. In the meantime, Harry filled Ron in about the package that seemed to have been moved from Gringotts to Hogwarts, and they spent a lot of time wondering what could possibly need such heavy protection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C9)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:10:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-9/</guid>
      <description>The Midnight Duel Harry had never believed he would meet a boy he hated more than Dudley, but that was before he met Draco Malfoy. Still, first-year Gryffindors only had Potions with the Slytherins, so they didn&amp;rsquo;t have to put up with Malfoy much. Or at least, they didn&amp;rsquo;t until they spotted a notice pinned up in the Gryffindor common room that made them all groan. Flying lessons would be starting on Thursday &amp;ndash; and Gryffindor and Slytherin would be learning together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone (C8)</title>
      <link>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 11:09:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://HBTghost.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/philosophers-stone-b1/chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>The Potions Master &amp;ldquo;There, look. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Where?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Next to the tall kid with the red hair. &amp;ldquo;
&amp;ldquo;Wearing the glasses?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Did you see his face?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Did you see his scar?&amp;rdquo;
Whispers followed Harry from the moment he left his dormitory the next day. People lining up outside classrooms stood on tiptoe to get a look at him, or doubled back to pass him in the corridors again, staring. Harry wished they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t, because he was trying to concentrate on finding his way to classes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>