<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chamber of Secrets (B2) on Oh, fixed it</title>
    <link>https://ohfix.github.io/tags/chamber-of-secrets-b2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chamber of Secrets (B2) on Oh, fixed it</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:26:49 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ohfix.github.io/tags/chamber-of-secrets-b2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C23)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:26:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-23/</guid>
      <description>“You saved her! You saved her! How did you do it?”
“I think we’d all like to know that,” said Professor McGonagall weakly.
Mrs. Weasley let go of Harry, who hesitated for a moment, then walked over to the desk and laid upon it the Sorting Hat, the ruby encrusted sword, and what remained of Riddle’s diary.
Then he started telling them everything. For nearly a quarter of an hour he spoke into the rapt silence: He told them about hearing the disembodied voice, how Hermione had finally realized that he was hearing a basilisk in the pipes; how he and Ron had followed the spiders into the forest, that Aragog had told them where the last victim of the basilisk had died; how he had guessed that Moaning Myrtle had been the victim, and that the entrance to the Chamber of Secrets might be in her bathroom…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C22)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:25:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-22/</guid>
      <description>“She won’t wake,” said a soft voice.
Harry jumped and spun around on his knees.
A tall, black haired boy was leaning against the nearest pillar, watching. He was strangely blurred around the edges, as though Harry were looking at him through a misted window. But there was no mistaking him—
“Tom—Tom Riddle?”
Riddle nodded, not taking his eyes off Harry’s face.
“What d’you mean, she won’t wake?” Harry said desperately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C21)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:24:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-21/</guid>
      <description>“My dear boy,” said Lockhart, straightening up and frowning at Harry. “Do use your common sense. My books wouldn’t have sold half as well if people didn’t think I’d done all those things. No one wants to read about some ugly old Armenian warlock, even if he did save a village from werewolves. He’d look dreadful on the front cover. No dress sense at all. And the witch who banished the Bandon Banshee had a harelip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C20)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:23:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-20/</guid>
      <description>His words were drowned by a loud outbreak of clicking and the rustling of many long legs shifting angrily; large black shapes shifted all around him.
“The thing that lives in the castle,” said Aragog, “is an ancient creature we spiders fear above all others. Well do I remember how I pleaded with Hagrid to let me go, when I sensed the beast moving about the school.”
“What is it?” said Harry urgently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C19)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:22:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-19/</guid>
      <description>“See here, Malfoy, if Dumbledore can’t stop them,” said Fudge, whose upper lip was sweating now, “I mean to say, who can?”
“That remains to be seen,” said Mr. Malfoy with a nasty smile. “But as all twelve of us have voted—”
Hagrid leapt to his feet, his shaggy black head grazing the ceiling.
“An’ how many did yeh have ter threaten an’ blackmail before they agreed, Malfoy, eh?” he roared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C18)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:21:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-18/</guid>
      <description>Dobby’s Reward Harry had been staring down the packed Gryffindor table, wondering if the new owner of Riddle’s diary was right in front of his eyes. Hermione had been urging him to report the robbery, but Harry didn’t like the idea. He’d have to tell a teacher all about the diary, and how many people knew why Hagrid had been expelled fifty years ago? He didn’t want to be the one who brought it all up again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C17)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:20:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-17/</guid>
      <description>The Heir of Slytherin Harry sat on his four-poster and flicked through the blank pages, not one of which had a trace of scarlet ink on it. Then he pulled a new bottle out of his bedside cabinet, dipped his quill into it, and dropped a blot onto the first page of the diary.
The ink shone brightly on the paper for a second and then, as though it was being sucked into the page, vanished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C16)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:19:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-16/</guid>
      <description>The Chamber of Secrets “What’s that?” asked Harry, pointing to something gold sticking out from under Hermione’s pillow.
“Just a get well card,” said Hermione hastily, trying to poke it out of sight, but Ron was too quick for her. He pulled it out, flicked it open, and read aloud:
“To Miss Granger, wishing you a speedy recovery, from your concerned teacher, Professor Gilderoy Lockhart, Order of Merlin, Third Class, Honorary Member of the Dark Force Defense League, and five time winner of Witch Weekly’s MostCharming Smile Award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C15)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:18:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-15/</guid>
      <description>Aragog As suddenly as it had started, everything stopped. Harry lay facedown on the stone cold floor, listening to Myrtle gurgling morosely in the end toilet. With difficulty, he kicked off his shoes and stood up. So this was what it felt like, being Goyle. His large hand trembling, he pulled off his old robes, which were hanging a foot above his ankles, pulled on the spare ones, and laced up Goyle’s boatlike shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (C14)</title>
      <link>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 23:17:49 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ohfix.github.io/posts/book/harry-potter/chamber-of-secrets-b2/chapter-14/</guid>
      <description>Cornelius Fudge He wasn’t alone after all. Standing on a golden perch behind the door was a decrepit looking bird that resembled a half plucked turkey. Harry stared at it and the bird looked balefully back, making its gagging noise again. Harry thought it looked very ill. Its eyes were dull and, even as Harry watched, a couple more feathers fell out of its tail.
Harry was just thinking that all he needed was for Dumbledore’s pet bird to die while he was alone in the office with it, when the bird burst into flames.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>